<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Regent College London News &#8211; Regent College London</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk</link>
	<description>HND Courses, Foundation Year, Top-Up and Bachelor Degrees</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 11:31:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Regent College London News &#8211; Regent College London</title>
	<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dr Bragagni presents on IEC MSB Strategic Seminar</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/dr-bragagni-presents-on-iec-msb-strategic-seminar/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/dr-bragagni-presents-on-iec-msb-strategic-seminar/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 03:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=89253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/dr-bragagni-presents-on-iec-msb-strategic-seminar/">Dr Bragagni presents on IEC MSB Strategic Seminar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_600f90b080629" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>On 19 January 2021, the IEC &#8211; International Electrotechnical Commission organised a virtual Strategic Seminar with members of MSB &#8211; Market Strategy Board, composed of 15 top-level technology officers appointed from leading industries all over the world. The aim of the seminar was to identify the principal technological trends and market needs in the IEC&#8217;s fields of activity.</p>
<p>Dr Maurizio Bragagni, CEO of Tratos UK Ltd and member of MSB-IEC, delivered a presentation on “Education on technologies”, which was prepared in close cooperation with Regent College London’s Head of Research, Dr Chris Wood. Dr Bragagni serves as the Chair of the Board of Governors at Regent College London.</p>
<p>Dr Bragagni’s presentation was followed with increased interest by the audience, as the use and impact of technology in education is extremely high, particularly in light of the significant disruption to education systems globally caused by the Covid-19 pandemic.</p>
<p>Throughout his presentation, drawing on the latest data available, Dr Bragagni emphasized the great potential of educational technology in providing enhanced access to educational content, enrichment experiences and learning communities as well as its role in making learning more interactive and collaborative, helping students to better engage with course material.</p>
<p>Starting from the 1990s, when computers became more commonplace in educational settings, the early 21st century has witnessed more widespread and commonplace educational use of PCs, laptops, tablets, smartphones, educational software, applications and online resources, especially in developed countries. As the century progresses, Augmented Reality (AR), Virtual Reality (VR) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are beginning to have a major impact on education.</p>
<p>Recent closures to educational settings forced on the world by the Covid-19 pandemic have put pressure on schools, universities, students and families to rapidly rethink traditional paradigms and embrace technology as an educational lifeline now and for the future.</p>
<p>There is now increasingly widespread recognition that digital technology has a fundamental role to play in future education systems alongside an urgent need to develop and implement high-quality and affordable technology-enabled programmes that ‘blend’ face to face and online learning.</p>
<p>Thanks to technology, the learning environment no longer has fixed boundaries. Instruction can be provided by any number of subject matter experts in addition to the person teaching a particular course.</p>
<p>While the technology-enabled teacher still needs to be ‘in the classroom’ (physical or virtual), their role is shifting from that of instructor &#8211; the sage on the stage &#8211; to facilitator and coach &#8211; the guide on the side.</p>
<p>Artificial Intelligence (AI) can help to personalise learning to an individual’s needs. For example, they can automate the e-learning feed, create recommendations based on individual learning history and help students to choose a future career based on data regarding their learning ability across subjects. At the same time, by analysing student’s data, teachers (or indeed AI systems) can better set the curriculum to match each student’s capability.</p>
<p>Dr Bragagni also warned that technology in itself, although undoubtedly a lifeline during the Covid-19 pandemic, is not a panacea. Technology must be used correctly to be effective, must be matched to the instructional environment and context. As well, it is especially important to strike the right balance between widening digital access and opportunity whilst at the same time ensuring that children are protected when online.</p>
<p>He brought to the attention of the audience recent data, illustrating the high variations in the world in relation to internet penetration, PC and smart phones ownership in households and warned that Covid-19 has highlighted stark inequalities between least developed countries and economically prosperous nations.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Dr Bragagni, as a successful entrepreneur and leader with strong focus on corporate social responsibility, stressed the importance of and offered his unconditional cooperation to working together with governments, academia, businesses and international organisations to narrow the dangerous gap of digital inequity in learning.</p>
<p>He asked the IEC to speed up the standardisation process, which could help in increasing accessibility and affordability to modern technology by all the countries of the world.</p>
<p>During the Q&#038;A session, the audience elaborated more on this request and asked for standardisation to be applied not only to the hardware, but as well to the software, which could make the e-learning platforms and tools accessible to all.</p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/dr-bragagni-presents-on-iec-msb-strategic-seminar/">Dr Bragagni presents on IEC MSB Strategic Seminar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/dr-bragagni-presents-on-iec-msb-strategic-seminar/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Learning Zone by School of Computing and Artificial Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-learning-zone-by-school-of-computing-and-artificial-intelligence/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-learning-zone-by-school-of-computing-and-artificial-intelligence/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 04:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=89030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-learning-zone-by-school-of-computing-and-artificial-intelligence/">The Learning Zone by School of Computing and Artificial Intelligence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_6000f08a97f08" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>It’s 2021 and Regent College London are excited to bring you The Learning Zone. Created by The <a href="/schools/school-of-computing-and-ai/">School of Computing &amp; AI</a>, the Learning Zone will feature monthly Guest Speaker events. We will be hosting guests from various industries to explore more about their life experiences, tips and tricks alongside a Q+A Session whereby attendees can ask to find out more! The sessions will take place at the end of each month, and we will be kicking off with our very first event on <strong>Friday 29th January 2021</strong>!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-large wp-image-89026" src="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence.jpg" alt=" The Learning Zone by School of Computing and Artificial Intelligence" width="100%" height="" srcset="https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence.jpg 1202w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-768x511.jpg 768w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-991x660.jpg 991w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-150x100.jpg 150w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-576x383.jpg 576w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-992x660.jpg 992w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/The-Learning-Zone-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-1200x799.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1202px) 100vw, 1202px" /></a><br />
The first event features Tara McBride, whom has many years of experience within the IT Industry. Tara was previously the Head of Computing at a London University and is currently an IT Manager. During the 1 Hour event, Tara will:</p>
<ol>
<li>Share her experiences in successfully working in the IT Industry</li>
<li>Share some ‘tips-to-success’ on how to use IT to help students and staff study and work effectively</li>
<li>Introduce a new Computing and AI Group: ‘Women in Computing’ – an important part of the new Computing Society.</li>
</ol>
<p>This will then be followed by an open Q+A Session.</p>
<p>We are excited to host Tara at the end of January and hope that both staff and students partake in the virtual event.</p>
<p>The full details of the event have been left below:</p>
<p><strong>When: Friday 29th January 2021 – From 5:00pm-6:00pm</strong></p>
<p><strong>Duration: 1 Hour</strong></p>
<p><strong>Link to attend: <a href="https://bit.ly/3oG6Gnf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://bit.ly/3oG6Gnf</a> </strong></p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-89066 size-medium" src="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-543x768.jpg" alt="Learning-Zone-event-launched" width="543" height="768" srcset="https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-543x768.jpg 543w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-700x991.jpg 700w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-768x1087.jpg 768w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-150x212.jpg 150w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-576x815.jpg 576w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence-992x1404.jpg 992w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Learning-Zone-event-launched-by-School-of-Computing-and-Artificial-Intelligence.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 543px) 100vw, 543px" /></p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-learning-zone-by-school-of-computing-and-artificial-intelligence/">The Learning Zone by School of Computing and Artificial Intelligence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-learning-zone-by-school-of-computing-and-artificial-intelligence/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Launch of The Power of Learning from DAD and Think and Grow Rich and digital learning platforms</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/launch-of-the-power-of-learning-from-dad-and-think-and-grow-rich-and-digital-learning-platforms/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/launch-of-the-power-of-learning-from-dad-and-think-and-grow-rich-and-digital-learning-platforms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=88831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/launch-of-the-power-of-learning-from-dad-and-think-and-grow-rich-and-digital-learning-platforms/">Launch of The Power of Learning from DAD and Think and Grow Rich and digital learning platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5fd6f22ee24ee" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>We are delighted to announce the launch of two new digital learning programmes: The Power of Learning from Dad and Think and Grow Rich.</p>
<p>The Power of Learning from DAD is a personal development programme, covering several the concepts essential to success, such as leadership, desire and Imagination. The second programme, Think and Grow Rich provides a summation of Napoleon Hill’s best-selling book of the same title, distilling Hill’s concepts in easy to understand and easy to implement steps.</p>
<p>Both programmes are written and presented by Dr. Selva Pankaj and add to the award-winning programme, Thinking into Character, as forms of asynchronous learning. With asynchronous learning, students can access lessons at any time, from any location and complete courses at their own pace. This form of delivery is part of our wider Regent Digital strategy, devised in March 2020, which embraces new technologies as a way of innovating education and bringing improved services to students and customers.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-88833" src="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms.jpg" alt="TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms" width="100%" height="" srcset="https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms.jpg 912w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms-768x354.jpg 768w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms-150x69.jpg 150w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TiC-POLD-and-TAGR-digital-learning-platforms-576x265.jpg 576w" sizes="(max-width: 912px) 100vw, 912px" /></a></p>
<p>On Wednesday 9 December, in a launch event attended by students, staff and invited guests, the latest additions to our personal development programmes went live. Members of the team demonstrated the new digital programmes, which are now updated and available to view on the platform <a href="https://www.tic.uk.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.tic.uk.com</a></p>
<p>The Power of Learning from DAD and Think and Grow Rich add breadth and depth to our existing digital programme, Thinking into Character. At the launch, all stakeholders in the Regent team, from students to lecturers to members of the Senior Leadership Team chose one concept from The Power of Learning from DAD and in their own ways described the significance of that concept to them.</p>
<p>Focusing on the need for students to incorporate these wider lessons as part of a holistic curriculum at Regent College London, Akosua Bonsu, Director of Studies for Thinking into Character and launch organiser, wrote:</p>
<p>“Successfully teaching subject knowledge is not enough for students to achieve the success that they desire as it is the ability to apply subject knowledge that leads to those successes. This ability to apply subject knowledge has to do with a students’ imagination, the capacity of their will, their ability to spot opportunities and so on. It is these ingredients, often missing from the taught curriculum, that we are aiming to deliver by means of these new digital programmes: The Power of Learning from Dad and Thinking and Grow Rich. In this way, Regent College London is a pioneer in closing the knowing-doing gap so prevalent in the education system and empowering students to achieve success”</p>
<p>We are delighted with the new additions The Power of Learning from Dad and Think and Grow Rich. As with Thinking into Character, a careful study of these programmes will develop in you the mindset required for success and self-fulfilment. You can review our new programmes here: <a href="https://www.tic.uk.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.tic.uk.com</a></p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/launch-of-the-power-of-learning-from-dad-and-think-and-grow-rich-and-digital-learning-platforms/">Launch of The Power of Learning from DAD and Think and Grow Rich and digital learning platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/launch-of-the-power-of-learning-from-dad-and-think-and-grow-rich-and-digital-learning-platforms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wealth Creation Programme launched</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wealth-creation-programme-launched/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wealth-creation-programme-launched/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 03:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=88679</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wealth-creation-programme-launched/">Wealth Creation Programme launched</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5fac9e049aaf6" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>Regent College London is delighted to announce the launch of our Wealth Creation Programme, as part of a series of initiatives to provide wider curriculum and pastoral support for our students during the global pandemic. </p>
<p>This programme is directed at all students, although particular focus is placed upon students who will be graduating from taught courses in 2021, and so entering a work environment characterised by a series of economic contractions.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
<a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london.jpg"><img src="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london.jpg" alt="Wealth Creation Programme for Students at Regent College London" width="100%" height="" class="alignleft size-full wp-image-88680" srcset="https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london.jpg 1202w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-768x511.jpg 768w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-991x660.jpg 991w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-150x100.jpg 150w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-576x383.jpg 576w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-992x660.jpg 992w, https://3arol9bs7qh145m57r5fbq9p-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/wealth-creation-programme-for-students-at-regent-college-london-1200x799.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1202px) 100vw, 1202px" /></a><br />
&nbsp;</p>
<p>Utilising many of the principles that underwrite <a href="http://www.tic.uk.com/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Thinking into Character</a>, including the principles that much of success is determined by mindset and that decisions rather than circumstances are the principal drivers of results, this programme will support students to transform their thinking around wealth and enterprise, in order that they may further develop a mindset conducive to wealth creation. </p>
<h2>What is a wealth conducive mindset?</h2>
<p>The first thing to note is that wealth is not always monetary in nature; wealth includes health, family and community relations. Inviting students to take a broad view on what wealth consists in is an important piece of the puzzle. Monetary wealth, and the principles required to achieve monetary wealth in times of economic crisis are also closely examined. Here the view is taken that our attitude to opportunity, our capacity to develop ourselves, and our ability to use our imaginations to engage in entrepreneurial ventures are critical to the creation of material wealth. Here students are learning to develop a new framework within which to prepare and plan for their next move as they leave <a href="/our-college/why-study-at-regent/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Regent College</a> and broaden their horizons in the world of work. </p>
<p>The programme, which launched last Saturday (7-11-2020), has gathered support from both students and teachers alike. In response to the question, “what did you learn from this lesson,” students commented:</p>
<p>“I learnt about money and I know now it’s all about flow, I learnt that there are laws that are involved in getting rich.” </p>
<p>“We all have equal opportunities to progress and achieve no matter where you are, and it is your mindset that directs you to your destiny.”  </p>
<p>“I am interested to learn more on the difference between man-made Laws &#038; the Universal Laws, which relate to the accumulation of wealth.” </p>
<p>The new Wealth Creation Programme is facilitated by the Principal of Regent College London and the CEO of Regent Group, Dr. Selva Pankaj. Dr. Selva has a long history of facilitating programmes that explore human capacities and human potential, having studied under Professor Clayton Christensen as part of his executive education at Harvard Business School.</p>
<p>The Wealth Creation Programme is available not just for our students, but to everyone. Find our more details of the programme <a href="https://www.tic.uk.com/wealth-creation-programme/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wealth-creation-programme-launched/">Wealth Creation Programme launched</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wealth-creation-programme-launched/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regent College London is now an Approved Fee Cap Provider</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-is-now-an-approved-fee-cap-provider/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-is-now-an-approved-fee-cap-provider/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 07:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=88003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-is-now-an-approved-fee-cap-provider/">Regent College London is now an Approved Fee Cap Provider</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5f30f389ff085" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>Regent College London was pleased to announce its registration with the Office for Students (OfS) and inclusion on its register in December 2018. Originally, Regent College London applied to become, and was successfully registered as, an Approved category provider.</p>
<p>As a result of guidance published by OfS regarding the process for changing category in March 2020, Regent College London had made the decision to apply to change category and become an Approved (Fee Cap) provider. We had made an application for this change to take effect for Academic Year 2020-21.</p>
<p>We are delighted to announce that our application was successful and Regent College London is now an Approved (Fee Cap).</p>
<p>This is an exciting time for Regent College London. Becoming an Approved Fee Cap provider is a part of our longer term strategic vision to move towards and apply for our own degree awarding powers.</p>
<p>The College will now benefit from grant funding and has also devised an Access and Participation Plan to improve equality of opportunity for underrepresented groups to access, succeed in and progress from higher education. To see our plan <a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/rcl-access-and-participation-plan.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p>The College already has great plans to put this into motion including initiatives such as a bursary scheme and providing all our students with a hand held device to ensure they are well equipped for the fast-moving digital era.</p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-is-now-an-approved-fee-cap-provider/">Regent College London is now an Approved Fee Cap Provider</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-is-now-an-approved-fee-cap-provider/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regent College London Moves to Phase 3</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-moves-to-phase-3/</link>
					<comments>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-moves-to-phase-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rasika Umamahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 15:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rcl.ac.uk/?p=87975</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-moves-to-phase-3/">Regent College London Moves to Phase 3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5f297a9fbb1f4" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>Regent College London are proud to announce that we will soon be moving to Phase 3 of our Five Stage System. The Five Stage System was created during the lockdown period and defines what studying at Regent College London will be like as we transition from the current situation to future learning and teaching. The stage that we are at will dictate which facilities and services will be open, and to what extent.</p>
<p>From the 20<sup>th</sup> March, we successfully implemented Regent Digital Services; a technological based learning ecosystem which has seen numerous lectures take place. We offer a range of degrees and their respective course types, including, Foundation Year Degrees, Bachelor Degrees, Top-up Degrees and Foundation Degrees. Our students have adapted incredibly well to learning digitally and thus will continue to provide this form of learning as we move into Phase 3.</p>
<p>Phase 3 consists of the first stage of reopening, which is likely to take place at the start of 2020/21, all teaching will take place via Regent Digital Services, with all 5 campuses in London, Harrow, Kingsbury, Southall and Wembley &#8211; open to limited services in a Covid Secure environment. Although student services will take place via Regent Digital Services, there will be new additional contact and arrangement methods in place and some socially-distanced activities.</p>
<p>Our students are the heartbeat of Regent College London and we ensure that their education with us will not be comprised in any shape, way or form. We have highly-professionally tutors that teach at high-standards, and we continue to provide digitally that to every student. As we move to Phase 3, we continue to monitor the situation at hand and follow Government Guidance.</p>
<p>For more information, please visit <a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/studying-at-regent/student-support/guidance-for-students-on-future-delivery/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a> or feel free to contact the Student Services Team on <a href="mailto:studentservices@rcl.ac.uk">studentservices@rcl.ac.uk</a> or 020 3897 3058.</p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-moves-to-phase-3/">Regent College London Moves to Phase 3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-moves-to-phase-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The left of centre approach</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-left-of-centre-approach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 05:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.regentcollegelondon.com/?p=87035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-left-of-centre-approach/">The left of centre approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[

<div id="general-content-block_5f00a60d2d730" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>Following a feature in the Independent Higher Education Webinar on Student Service and mental health offered during Covid-19, Akosua Bonsu, Director of Studies for Thinking into Character, writes about the connection of <a href="http://www.tic.uk.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Thinking into Character</a> to positive mental health outcomes.</p>
<h2>#MentalHealth is not an add-on</h2>
<p>Mental health concerns are likely to emerge or to be compounded in lockdown. Being stuck indoors, being unable to see family members, attempting to home educate children, working in frontline services or the financial strain of being furloughed, all add to an unprecedented cocktail of triggers for anxiety and depression.<br />
In this context, educational institutions cannot afford to think of the mental health services that they offer to students as supplementary or optional. At this time, the mental health and the mental wellbeing of students must feature as an integral part of the service each college provides. At Regent College London, one way we have done this is by embedding Thinking into Character, an award winning personal and professional development programme (PPD), into the teaching and learning for all students.</p>
<h2>Personal Development and the methodology of Cognitive Behavioural Therapy</h2>
<p>We do not usually think of PPD in relation to mental health and wellbeing, so how can a PPD programme like Thinking into Character support mental health?<br />
That connection between Thinking into Character and mental health comes via the methodology of Cognitive Behavioural Therapy (CBT). NHS England describes CBT as follows:<br />
“Cognitive behavioural therapy (CBT) is a talking therapy that can help you manage your problems by changing the way you think and behave. It&#8217;s most commonly used to treat <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/generalised-anxiety-disorder/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">anxiety</a> and <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/clinical-depression/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">depression</a>, but can be useful for other mental and physical health problems”. <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/cognitive-behavioural-therapy-cbt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">(NHS, 2020)</a><br />
CBT is essentially a talking therapy rooted in the view that we can change mental health outcomes by changing the way we think. Thinking into Character adopts the methodology of Cognitive Behavioural Therapy. The key principle underlying the programme is that we change our results by changing the way we think. To that end, many of the exercises involved Thinking into Character involves shifting thinking, in a manner analogous to CBT programmes.<br />
Read full article of FE News <a href="https://www.fenews.co.uk/featured-article/47502-left-of-centre-supporting-positive-mental-health-outcomes-during-lockdown" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.fenews.co.uk/featured-article/47502-left-of-centre-supporting-positive-mental-health-outcomes-during-lockdown</a></p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/the-left-of-centre-approach/">The left of centre approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regent College London takes part in weekly #clapforcarers</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-takes-part-in-weekly-clapforcarers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pubudu Mahesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 23:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.regentcollegelondon.com/?p=86803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s important to stick together and do what we can to help those on the frontline. The staff at Regent College London took part in the weekly #clapforcarers to show our continued support for our brilliant NHS key workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-takes-part-in-weekly-clapforcarers/">Regent College London takes part in weekly #clapforcarers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5f00a71ce0346" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>During such tough and draining times, we are incredibly happy to see the positivity and light that the nation is bringing. It’s important to stick together and do what we can to help those on the frontline. The staff at Regent College London took part in the weekly #clapforcarers to show our continued support for our brilliant NHS key workers. We cannot thank them enough for risking their lives to save ours. To everyone working to keeping the country going, we thank you!</p>
<style type="text/css">.post-featured{ display:none; } </style>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>


<div id="media-two-up-block_606ee8ec91222" class="web-block media-two-up">
    <div class="row row--layout-left">
		<!-- Media cell -->
		<div class="mtu-cell mtu-cell--media">
							<iframe type="text/html" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LjE_o3qmnVc" frameborder="0"></iframe>
					</div>
		<!-- Content cell -->
        <div class="mtu-cell mtu-cell--content">
			<div class="rich-text">
                <h6></h6>
                <h2></h2>
                <p></p>
			</div>
			        </div>

    </div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/regent-college-london-takes-part-in-weekly-clapforcarers/">Regent College London takes part in weekly #clapforcarers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>COVID-19 self isolation tips for students</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/covid-19-self-isolation-tips-for-students/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sangeeth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 23:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.regentcollegelondon.com/?p=86783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/covid-19-self-isolation-tips-for-students/">COVID-19 self isolation tips for students</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="general-content-block_5f0049bb1eeaa" class="web-block general-content">








	    <div class="rich-text top-row ">
				
					    </div>







		<div class="bottom-row  bottom-row--have-sidebar ">
	        <div class="bottom-row__inner rich-text"><p>News of Coronavirus has been around for a few months now but it’s only in the last couple of weeks that it has really started to hit us hard here in the UK.<br />
The speed of change has been head-spinning causing confusion and anxiety. Many people are taking it seriously – many are not – and this is causing conflict and distress. And, for some of us, it is affecting our family and our friends directly causing worry and grief.</p>
<p>These are strange times for sure and, with no end in sight, it is inevitable that in addition to the current physical health risks there is also a heightened risk to our mental health.</p>
<p>So, we have put together the guide to help support you during these uncertain times on our mental health support app- MIND CONNECT.<br />
If you haven’t downloaded it yet – this is the right time to do so. Please download free app Zappar on your phone, scan Mind Connect logo at the back of your ID card, click on the COVID 19 information and check the top tips for staying in mentally good shape throughout this challenging time.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>

			            	<div class="bottom-row__sidebar side-cards">
									</div>
					</div>







</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/covid-19-self-isolation-tips-for-students/">COVID-19 self isolation tips for students</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NSS survey winners announced</title>
		<link>https://www.rcl.ac.uk/nss-survey-winners-announced/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sangeeth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 08:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regent College London News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.regentcollegelondon.com/?p=86769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Each year, the National Student Survey (NSS) gives our final year students the opportunity to reflect on their experience at Regent College London and provide feedback about their course. As part of the Regent College&#160; NSS promotional campaign, eligible students had a chance to be entered into our prize draw to win one of 12 &#8230; <a href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/nss-survey-winners-announced/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/nss-survey-winners-announced/">NSS survey winners announced</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Each year, the National Student Survey (NSS) gives our final year students the opportunity to reflect on their experience at Regent College London and provide feedback about their course.<br />
As part of the Regent College&nbsp; NSS promotional campaign, eligible students had a chance to be entered into our prize draw to win one of 12 prizes of £50 Amazon vouchers.<br />
The prize draw has been now&nbsp; closed&nbsp; and we are pleased to announce the winners below:</p>
<div class="u-responsive-table">
<table style="margin: 20px 0;" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>FE00285</td>
<td>HE05581</td>
<td>HE06492</td>
<td>HE06621</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>HE06681</td>
<td>HE06703</td>
<td>HE06741</td>
<td>HE06821</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>HE07048</td>
<td>HE07080</td>
<td>HE07116</td>
<td>HE07138</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p>The lucky&nbsp; winners will get their vouchers via e-mail next week. Congratulations to the winners and thanks all who took part in the survey.</p>
<style type="text/css">.post-featured{ display:none; } </style>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk/nss-survey-winners-announced/">NSS survey winners announced</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.rcl.ac.uk">Regent College London</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
